{
    "250": {
        "3": {
            "3": {
                "correct": "1984",
                "question": "When is the Rwanda's first appearance at the Olympic games ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "1984"
                },
                "id": 25033,
                "valid": true
            },
            "1": {
                "correct": "Amavubi(The wasps)",
                "question": "What is the name of the Rwandan soccer team ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Amavubi(The wasps)"
                },
                "id": 25031,
                "valid": true
            },
            "2": {
                "correct": "93rd",
                "question": "What is the FIFA ranking of the Rwandan national soccer team ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "93rd"
                },
                "id": 25032,
                "valid": true
            }
        },
        "1": {
            "3": {
                "correct": "JuvA(c)nal Habyarimana",
                "question": "Who was the president of Rwanda in 1994 ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "JuvA(c)nal Habyarimana"
                },
                "id": 25013,
                "valid": true
            },
            "1": {
                "correct": "Paul Kagame",
                "question": "Who is the President of Rwanda ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Paul Kagame"
                },
                "id": 25011,
                "valid": false
            },
            "2": {
                "correct": "Silas Lwakabamba",
                "question": "Who is the Minister of education of Rwanda?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Silas Lwakabamba"
                },
                "id": 25012,
                "valid": true
            }
        },
        "5": {
            "3": {
                "correct": "Tutsis and Hutus",
                "question": "What are the two main tribes of Rwanda ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Tutsis and Hutus"
                },
                "id": 25053,
                "valid": true
            },
            "1": {
                "correct": "Itorero",
                "question": "Name the main traditional Rwandan dance ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Itorero"
                },
                "id": 25051,
                "valid": true
            },
            "2": {
                "correct": "Afrobeat",
                "question": "What is the most modern music genre in Rwanda ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Afrobeat"
                },
                "id": 25052,
                "valid": true
            }
        },
        "2": {
            "3": {
                "correct": "638.67 US dollars(2013)",
                "question": "What is the GDP per capita of Rwanda ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "638.67 US dollars(2013)"
                },
                "id": 25023,
                "valid": true
            },
            "1": {
                "correct": "Rwandan Franc",
                "question": "What is the currency of Rwanda ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Rwandan Franc"
                },
                "id": 25021,
                "valid": true
            },
            "2": {
                "correct": "Tea",
                "question": "What is the main cash crop of Rwanda ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Tea"
                },
                "id": 25022,
                "valid": true
            }
        },
        "4": {
            "3": {
                "correct": "Rwanda Nziza",
                "question": "What is the name of the Rwandan national anthem ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Rwanda Nziza"
                },
                "id": 25043,
                "valid": true
            },
            "1": {
                "correct": "knowless",
                "question": "Who sang baramushaka ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "knowless"
                },
                "id": 25041,
                "valid": true
            },
            "2": {
                "correct": "Jean-Paul Samputu",
                "question": "Who won two kora awards in 2003 for \"Most Inspiring\" and \"Best Traditional Artist\" ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Jean-Paul Samputu"
                },
                "id": 25042,
                "valid": true
            }
        }
    },
    "243": {
        "3": {
            "3": {
                "correct": "Kabuscorp SCP",
                "question": "What team does Tresor Mputu Mabi play for currently ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Kabuscorp SCP"
                },
                "id": 24333,
                "valid": true
            },
            "1": {
                "correct": "Fimbu",
                "question": "What was teh DR Congo national team known for at the just ended 2017 AFCON ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Fimbu"
                },
                "id": 24331,
                "valid": true
            },
            "2": {
                "correct": "2009 and 2010",
                "question": "In what years did TP Mazembe win the CAF Champions league back to back ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "2009 and 2010"
                },
                "id": 24332,
                "valid": true
            }
        },
        "1": {
            "3": {
                "correct": "2001",
                "question": "Since when has Joseph KAbila been the President of DR.Congo?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "2001"
                },
                "id": 24313,
                "valid": true
            },
            "1": {
                "correct": "Joseph Kasavubu",
                "question": "Who was the first President of DR Congo?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Joseph Kasavubu"
                },
                "id": 24311,
                "valid": true
            },
            "2": {
                "correct": "1960",
                "question": " In which year did DR Congo gain independence ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "1960"
                },
                "id": 24312,
                "valid": true
            }
        },
        "5": {
            "3": {
                "correct": "Kingwana",
                "question": "What is the DR Congo dialect of Swahili called ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Kingwana"
                },
                "id": 24353,
                "valid": true
            },
            "1": {
                "correct": "242",
                "question": "How many languages are spoken in DR Congo?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "242"
                },
                "id": 24351,
                "valid": true
            },
            "2": {
                "correct": "Pygmies",
                "question": "Which ethnic group are the earliest inhabitants of Congo ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Pygmies"
                },
                "id": 24352,
                "valid": true
            }
        },
        "2": {
            "3": {
                "correct": "784 US dollars(2013)",
                "question": "What is the GDP per capita of DR congo ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "784 US dollars(2013)"
                },
                "id": 24323,
                "valid": true
            },
            "1": {
                "correct": "Congolese Franc",
                "question": "What is the currency of DR Congo?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Congolese Franc"
                },
                "id": 24321,
                "valid": true
            },
            "2": {
                "correct": "cobalt ore",
                "question": "What mineral is produced in large quantities by DR Congo?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "cobalt ore"
                },
                "id": 24322,
                "valid": true
            }
        },
        "4": {
            "3": {
                "correct": "Joseph Lutumba",
                "question": "Who composed the DR Congo National anthem ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Joseph Lutumba"
                },
                "id": 24343,
                "valid": true
            },
            "1": {
                "correct": "Emenaya",
                "question": "Who sang Nzinzi ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Emenaya"
                },
                "id": 24341,
                "valid": true
            },
            "2": {
                "correct": "Soukous",
                "question": "What is the popular name for Congolese music ?",
                "answers": {
                    "1": "Soukous"
                },
                "id": 24342,
                "valid": true
            }
        }
    }
}